

Məhəmmədəli Əliyev

BACK-END DEVELOPER

- Paku, Azerbaijan
- mehemmedeli678@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/məhəmmədəli-əliyev-271573235/

055-880-67-76

SKILLS

- Asp .Net Core (MVC & API)
- C#
- OOP and SOLID Principles
- Nlayer Arcitecture
- Node JS (Express)
- SQL (MS-SQL)
- No-SQL (Mongo, Firestore)
- HTML,CSS,SCSS
- GIT & GitHub

LANGUAGE

- English
- Turkish

ABOUT ME

An experienced website developer specializing in websites .Have done numerous projects involving front and backend development. Innovative Full-stack developer more than two years experience building and maintaining responsive web sites, plus modern libraries and frameworks .

WORK EXPERIENCE

BACK-END DEVELOPER

Websuper agency

Sep 2021 - Oct 2022

- Api with Node Js(Express)
- Database with Firebase and Mongo db
- Vue JS (Nuxt Js)

BACK-END DEVELOPER

Oct 2020 - Avg 2021

Webcoder

- Asp .Net Core (MVC & API)
- SQL server(MS-SQL)

EDUCATION HISTORY

Bachaleor Finance

UNEC

2017-2021

Compar Academy

Full-Stack Developer

Dec 2019 -Dec 2020

- Front-End(HTML,CSS,SCSS,JS,Jquery,Bootstrap)
- Back-End(Asp .Net Core(MVC&API),MS-SQL,C#,Windows Form,)
- SQL Server(Procedures etc.)

GİTHUB ACOUNT



https://github.com/mehemmedeli678